<BRANDON HAWLEY>

Independence, MO 64055 (816) 745-8170 bhawley45@gmail.com









A passionate game developer with six years of software development experience, including two years specializing in Unreal Engine 5 and Unity. Dedicated to pushing the boundaries of game design and player experience, eager to learn from others and contribute my unique mix of creativity and passion.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Game Developer Intern (Full-Time)

Proper IT Consulting | 4/2023 - 1/2024

Developed games and software using Unreal Engine 5, Unity, C#, and web languages. Demonstrated proficiency in version control and project management in a fast-paced development environment.

IT Specialist (Contract)

Cumoratek Consulting | 6/2023 - 1/2024

Provided IT services at a private school, managing student databases and enhancing website compatibility, deploying Linux and Windows servers, and repairing school devices.

Business Owner (Full-Time)

Hawleywood Electronics LLC | 1/2018 - 3/2022

Founded an LLC specializing in computer and electronics repair, with key roles in hardware and software troubleshooting. Managed all business aspects including finances and client communication.

General Manager (Full-Time)

Archery Excellence | 5/2016 - 3/2019

Provided education across various roles, overseeing event scheduling, employee management, and operational tasks. Offering mentorship to team members and technical support for both archery and tech equipment.

Creative Director (Part-Time)

Youtube: ObviouslyBrandon | 1/2022 - Present

Currently manage a gaming YouTube channel with a reasonable following. Gained experience in video editing, script writing, and engagement algorithms.

SKILLS & PROFICIENCIES

Languages: C++, C#, Java, JavaScript, HTML, CSS Game Dev Tools: Unreal Engine 4 & 5, Unity Creative Software: DaVinci Resolve 18, GIMP

Version Control: Git, GitHub, SourceTree Project Management: Agile/Scrum

IDEs: Visual Studio, JetBrains(IntelliJ, Rider) Frameworks/Libraries: .NET, Bootstrap, SwiperJs,

jQuery, Raylib

Databases: SQL Server, mySQL

EDUCATION

Certification in Software & Game Development

The Tech Academy | 1/24/2024 **Graduated with honors.** Completed an intensive program with 900+ hours of instruction and hands-on projects in software and game development with accompanying Internship.

CompTIA A+ Certification

Metropolitan Community College | 12/11/2018

Bachelor of Computer Science

Metropolitan Community College | 2018 - 2019 Missouri Western State University | 2019 - 2020

Phi-Theta-Kappa Honor Society

Recognized for proficiency in Java and statistics. I was also invited to tutor Java. My studies were cut short due to COVID-19.

/GAMEPLAY /DEVELOPER